https://mocorn.org/privacy-policy/

Who we are
Missouri Corn Growers AssociationMissouri Corn Merchandising Council3118 Emerald LaneJefferson City, MO 65109PHONE: (800) 827-4181FAX: (573) 893-4612
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Certain functions on our website require us to collect personal data from our users in order to do general business. Examples of personal data collected include (but not limited to) name, phone number, email address, physical and/or mailing address, fax, and membership information. Information such as this is necessary to provide our website visitors with membership registration, event registration, and contact requests submitted through our website, among other functions and submission forms available to our visitors. When you initiate contact with Missouri Corn Growers Association through submitting a form on this website, your consent for collection and retention of this information for normal business usage is implied.
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the
comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy
is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of
your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the
context of your comment.
Cookies/User Sessions
If
you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name,
email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave
another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
Embedded content from other websites
Content on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, links, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party
tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including
tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and
are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Information about our website visitors is also collected through the use of Google Analytics. That software collects information about our visitors such as pages visited, duration of time on site, browser and general device information, etc. We use these statistical tools to analyze our website’s usefulness to our visitors and make improvements when needed. Google’s privacy policy can be found here.
Who we share your data with
Information, as described above, is collected for Missouri Corn Growers Association’s business needs. We do not share or sell your contact information with any third parties. We partner with Insight Marketing Design to host and maintain our website, and as such, they have full access to information collected and stored through our website. This partnership is necessary to maintain and improve our website services. Website administrators also have full access to data collected and stored by Missouri Corn Growers Association’s website.
How long we retain your data
Data
collected, as described above, is retained indefinitely for customer service
purposes and as storage space allows.
What rights you have over your data
If you have submitted contact or registration forms on this website, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Data related to our website is held on a secured web server in the USA.
Our contact information
Missouri Corn Growers AssociationMissouri Corn Merchandising Council3118 Emerald LaneJefferson City, MO 65109PHONE: (800) 827-4181FAX: (573) 893-4612
Additional information
How we protect your data
Our hosting company uses a secure firewall to keep out unauthorized users and ensure the integrity of our systems. We are vigilant about protecting our site from unwanted intrusions.
In this section:
